Guide to the Bruce Voeller papers, 1956-1990
Voeller, Bruce papers, 1956-1990
- Series II. Early Scientific Research
  - Payne, Donald, "A Study of Flower Coloration and its Distribution in Mimulus Whitneyi", 1956 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Fern articles (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Voeller, Bruce, "Variation in Mimulus Whitneyi" (thesis), 1956 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Voeller, Bruce, "Crozier Uncoiling in Ferns" (thesis), 1961 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Voeller, Bruce, "The Plant Cell: Aspects of its Form and Function" (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Voeller, Bruce, "The Plant Cell" cont'd (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Voeller, Bruce: Publications about Fern and Plant Research, 1963-1971 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Sexual Reproduction In Ferns, 16mm film, F-801 (Box 66)
  - Edward S. Burgess, Green and Brown Algae, 1882; Plant specimens (Box 64)
  - Edward S. Burgess, Red Algae, 1882; Plant specimens (Box 65)
  - AIDS/ Barrier Contraception Results, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Anderson and Voeller- Spermacide, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Clinical Studies, 1977-1988 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Correct Use/Brochures/Inserts, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Failure, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Condoms, 1987-1988 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Permits- New York City, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Rankings-Condoms, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Reviews-Condoms, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Segal, 1980-1984 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Test Results-Various, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 11-13)
  - Use- How To, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - "Homosexual Behavior", 1980 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Gay Pride Proclamation, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous (Includes Paper by Voeller), 1970-1980 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - National Gay Task Force Membership, 1978-1979 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - National Gay Task Force Memos, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - National Gay Task Force Symposium, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - New National Resolutions, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - People: Voeller, 1973-1990 (Box 54, Folder 6-7)
  - People: Voeller Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - People: Voeller, Personal, 1978-1979 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Psychiatry, N.D. (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Support Letters, 1976-1978 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Surveys, 1978-1979 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Volunteers, 1975-1977 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - AIDS Pamphlets (assorted) (Box 58)
  - Condom Survey Dataset (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Gay Movement Buttons (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - White Tube From "Tubed Products Inc." (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Tahiti Condoms and Packaging (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - "Coming Out" Some Kind of Printing Block w/ Picture of B.V. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Gold Circle Condoms (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - PrePair Tube (From "Tube" File) (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Gay Movement Buttons (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Veto-Prophylactic Tube and Package, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Betadine Douche and Packaging, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Ramses Packaging, N.D. (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Lifestyles Packaging, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Mentor Condoms, Instructions, ADS, Packaging, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - "Card Tricks" Playing Card Decks (2) (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - What You Don't Know CAN Hurt You (Deadly Diseases/ Surprising Solutions) by Stewart F. Hughes (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Stonewall Speech, May 1992 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Gay Movement Buttons (Box 60, Folder 1-8)
  - "Homosexuality: The Last Debate" Poster, 5 posters (Box 62)
  - "Celebration '83: Celebrating Louisiana Gay Pride Week in New Orleans!", 1983; 1 signed poster (12 signatures) (Box 62)
  - "Matrix Man" News Article from "Gay News" (Box 62)
  - "The National Observer", April 1973; Newspaper (Box 62)
  - Newspaper article featuring piece on sketch portraits of Mariposa figures (Box 62)
- Series III. Recordings
  - Plenary-AIDS: Update and Prevention, Mckusick, Voeller, Wyatt, tr7834a
  - Bruce Voeller and Evelyn Hooker, April 23, 1980; tr7835a-b
  - "Defamation" Narrated by Harvey Fierstein for GLAAD, Audio Cassette (Box 61)
  - Don Hicks-CDC, March 1985; Audio Cassette (Box 61)
  - Don Hicks (continued), March 1985; Audio Cassette (Box 61)
  - AIDS and Sex (David R. Bolling, M.D., FACOG), December 1987; Audio Cassette (Box 61)
  - Bill Darrow-CDC, April 1985; Audio Cassette (Box 61)
  - Don Hicks, August 1985; Audio Cassette (Box 61)
  - AIDS and Sex, Bruce Voeller, Ph.D., December 1987; Audio Cassette (Box 61)
  - Plenary- AIDS: Update and Prevention (McKusick, Voeller, Wyatt), Audio Cassette (Box 61)
  - Hick, Frames, Voeller Conference Call (CDC), Audio Cassette (Box 61)
  - Don Hicks, June 1985; Audio Cassette (Box 61)
  - National Gay Task Force, Audio Cassette (Box 61)
  - Symposium- Sexuality and the American Indian Internal and External Influences, Audio Cassette (Box 61)
  - AIDS and Sex, Margaret Nichols, Ph.D., December 1987; Audio Cassette (Box 61)
  - Don Hicks, CDC, February 1985 (Box 61)
  - MJ Potash I.O.M., Audio Cassette (Box 61)
  - Wandell Pommercy and Bruce Voeller, June 1980; Audio Cassette (Box 61)
  - Three Darwin Songs- Richard Milner, 1992; Audio Cassette (Box 61)
  - KABC Radio Show- Voeller/Cameron, Paul. Tom Al... on Ray Brean Show, 1985; Audio Cassette (Box 61)
  - Chip Cullman, February 1989; Audio Cassette (Box 61)
  - AIDS and Safer Sex, Audio Cassette (Box 61)
  - Gray Davis, Audio Cassette (Box 61)
  - "Should Homosexuality Be in the APA Nomenclature?" (Audio-Digest: Psychiatry Vol. 2 No. 11), Audio Cassette (Box 61)